Mana: Beyond Belief documentary film collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 6: United States
  - Memphis (Tenn.), August 14-17, 2002
    - Moving Images
      - HDCAM Tape 44, 2002-08-15 to 2002-08-16, AFC 2019/001: MV044; afc2019001_0044; 49 min.; 25th anniversary of Elvis Presley's death, Elvis Presley impersonators, Graceland Mansion
      - HDCAM Tape 45, 2002-08-16, AFC 2019/001: MV045; afc2019001_0045; 49 min.; 25th anniversary of Elvis Presley's death, Elvis Presley impersonators
      - HDCAM Tape 46, 2002-08-16 to 2002-08-17, AFC 2019/001: MV046; afc2019001_0046; 48 min.; 25th anniversary of Elvis Presley's death, Elvis Presley impersonators, Graceland Mansion, Nigel Kingsley
    - Sound Recordings
      - DAT Tape 39, 2002-08-14, AFC 2019/001: SR039; afc2019001_DAT0039; 16 min.; 25th anniversary of Elvis Presley's death, Elvis Presley impersonators
      - DAT Tape 39A, 2002-08-14, AFC 2019/001: SR039A; afc2019001_DAT0039A; 1 hr. 29 min.; 25th anniversary of Elvis Presley's death, Elvis Presley impersonators
      - DAT Tape 39B, 2002-08-14, AFC 2019/001: SR039B; afc2019001_DAT0039B; 1 hr. 28 min.; 25th anniversary of Elvis Presley's death, Elvis Presley impersonators
      - DAT Tape 39C, 2002-08-14, AFC 2019/001: SR039C; afc2019001_DAT0039C; 1 hr. 23 min.; 25th anniversary of Elvis Presley's death, Elvis Presley impersonators
      - DAT Tape 40, 2002-08-14 to 2002-08-15, AFC 2019/001: SR040; afc2019001_DAT0040; 1 hr. 28 min.; 25th anniversary of Elvis Presley's death, Elvis Presley impersonators
      - DAT Tape 41, 2002-08-15 to 2002-08-16, AFC 2019/001: SR041; afc2019001_DAT0041; 1 hr. 37 min.; 25th anniversary of Elvis Presley's death, Graceland Mansion, Holiday Inn
      - DAT Tape 42, 2002-08-16 to 2002-08-17, AFC 2019/001: SR042; afc2019001_DAT0042; 1 hr. 36 min.; 25th anniversary of Elvis Presley's death, Graceland Mansion, Elvis Presley impersonators, Holiday Inn
  - Sumpter (Wis.), August 19-22, 2002
    - Manuscripts
      - Transcriptions, circa 2003-04, 107 pages; English (Box-folder 2/3)
      - Transcriptions, circa 2003-04, 06_USA_Sumpter_Transcriptions; 2 files (.pdf); English (Digital-content afc2019001_dc002)
      - Post-production documentation, 2003-10-14, 10 pages; "décollage," "Evermor et Jacob," "Forevertron," "Itv Dr Evermor," "Spectateurs et autres oeuvres," "The birds' band" (Box-folder 2/4)
    - Moving Images
      - HDCAM Tape 47, 2002-08-19, AFC 2019/001: MV047; afc2019001_0047; 49 min.; Dr. Evermor's Forevertron
      - HDCAM Tape 48, 2002-08-19, AFC 2019/001: MV048; afc2019001_0048; 49 min.; Dr. Evermor's Forevertron
      - HDCAM Tape 49, 2002-08-19 to 2002-08-20, AFC 2019/001: MV049; afc2019001_0049; 52 min.; Dr. Evermor's Forevertron, Tom Every
      - HDCAM Tape 50, 2002-08-19 to 2002-08-20, AFC 2019/001: MV050; afc2019001_0050; 49 min.; Dr. Evermor's Forevertron, Tom Every
      - HDCAM Tape 51, 2002-08-20, AFC 2019/001: MV051; afc2019001_0051; 50 min.; Dr. Evermor's Forevertron
      - HDCAM Tape 52, 2002-08-20 to 2002-08-22, AFC 2019/001: MV052; This item is also listed in Series 6, Chicago (Ill.).; afc2019001_0052; 49 min.; Dr. Evermor's Forevertron, Chicago Mercantile Exchange
    - Sound Recordings
      - DAT Tape 43, 2002-08-19 to 2002-08-20, AFC 2019/001: SR043; afc2019001_DAT0043; 1 hr. 39 min.; Dr. Evermor's Forevertron, Tom Every
      - DAT Tape 44, 2002-08-19 to 2002-08-20, AFC 2019/001: SR044; afc2019001_DAT0044; 1 hr. 21 min.; Dr. Evermor's Forevertron, Tom Every
  - Chicago (Ill.), August 20-22, 2002
    - Manuscripts
      - Post-production documentation, 2003-10-14, 3 pages; "Chicago exchange" (Box-folder 2/5)
    - Moving Images
      - HDCAM Tape 52, 2002-08-20 to 2002-08-22, AFC 2019/001: MV052; This item is also listed in Series 6, Sumpter (Wis.).; afc2019001_0052; 49 min.; Dr. Evermor's Forevertron, Chicago Mercantile Exchange
      - HDCAM Tape 53, 2002-08-22, AFC 2019/001: MV053; afc2019001_0053; 36 min.; Chicago Mercantile Exchange
    - Sound Recordings
      - DAT Tape 45, 2002-08-22, AFC 2019/001: SR045; afc2019001_DAT0045; 1 hr. 31 min.; Chicago Mercantile Exchange
  - Española (N.M.), August 24-25, 2002
    - Manuscripts
      - Transcriptions, circa 2003-04, 27 pages; English (Box-folder 2/6)
      - Transcriptions, 2003-04-22 to 2003-05-18, 06_USA_Espanola_Transcriptions; 3 files (.doc); English (Digital-content afc2019001_dc002)
      - Post-production documentation, 2003-10-14, 9 pages; "Low Riders," "Low Lows' painted cars," "Lowriders at night" (Box-folder 2/7)
    - Moving Images
      - HDCAM Tape 54, 2002-08-24, AFC 2019/001: MV054; afc2019001_0054; 48 min.; Lowriders
      - HDCAM Tape 55, 2002-08-24, AFC 2019/001: MV055; This item is also listed in Series 6, Chimayo (N.M.).; afc2019001_0055; 48 min.; Lowriders, Santuario de Chimayo
      - HDCAM Tape 56, 2002-08-24, AFC 2019/001: MV056; afc2019001_0056; 51 min.; Lowriders, Arthur Medina
      - HDCAM Tape 57, 2002-08-24 to 2002-08-25, AFC 2019/001: MV057; This item is also listed in Series 6, Chimayo (N.M.).; afc2019001_0057; 47 min.; Lowriders, Santuario de Chimayo
    - Sound Recordings
      - DAT Tape 46, 2002-08-24, AFC 2019/001: SR046; afc2019001_DAT0046; 1 hr. 36 min.; Lowriders
      - DAT Tape 47, 2002-08-24, AFC 2019/001: SR047; afc2019001_DAT0047; 29 min.; Lowriders
  - Chimayo (N.M.), August 24-27, 2002
    - Manuscripts
      - Translations and transcriptions, circa 2003-04, 13 pages; Spanish, English (Box-folder 2/8)
      - Post-production documentation, 2003-10-14, 5 pages; "CHIMAYO Church" (Box-folder 2/9)
    - Moving Images
      - HDCAM Tape 55, 2002-08-24, AFC 2019/001: MV055; This item is also listed in Series 6, Espanola (N.M.).; afc2019001_0055; 48 min.; Lowriders, Santuario de Chimayo
      - HDCAM Tape 57, 2002-08-24 to 2002-08-25, AFC 2019/001: MV057; This item is also listed in Series 6, Espanola (N.M.).; afc2019001_0057; 47 min.; Lowriders, Santuario de Chimayo
      - HDCAM Tape 58, 2002-08-25, AFC 2019/001: MV058; afc2019001_0058; 44 min.; Santuario de Chimayo
      - HDCAM Tape 59, 2002-08-25, AFC 2019/001: MV059; afc2019001_0059; 49 min.; Santuario de Chimayo
      - HDCAM Tape 60, 2002-08-25 to 2002-08-27, AFC 2019/001: MV060; This item is also listed in Series 6, Navajo Nation.; afc2019001_0060; 48 min.; Santuario de Chimayo, Navajo hogan
    - Sound Recordings
      - DAT Tape 48, 2002-08-25, AFC 2019/001: SR048; afc2019001_DAT0048; 1 hr. 28 min.; Santuario de Chimayo, Lowriders
      - DAT Tape 49, 2002-08-25, AFC 2019/001: SR049; afc2019001_DAT0049; 52 min.; Santuario de Chimayo
  - Navajo Nation, August 25-September 1, 2002
    - Manuscripts
      - Translations and transcriptions, 2003-06-01 to 2003-07-11, 06_USA_NavajoNation_Translations and transcriptions; 10 files (.pdf, .doc, plain text); Navajo, English (Digital-content afc2019001_dc002)
      - Post-production documentation, 2003-10-14, 14 pages; "Itv Kee in kitchen," "Kee's Hogan Jour," "Cérémonie Angus," "Fabrication Tambour," "Habit rituel," "Life around the Hogan," "Songs+kids," "Sweat Lodge," "Landscapes" (Box-folder 2/10)
    - Moving Images
      - HDCAM Tape 60, 2002-08-25 to 2002-08-27, AFC 2019/001: MV060; This item is also listed in Series 6, Chimayo (N.M.).; afc2019001_0060; 48 min.; Santuario de Chimayo, Navajo hogan
      - HDCAM Tape 61, 2002-08-28, AFC 2019/001: MV061; afc2019001_0061; 48 min.; Navajo hogan, Kee Zonnie, Buddy Redmustache
      - HDCAM Tape 62, 2002-08-29, AFC 2019/001: MV062; afc2019001_0062; 49 min.; Navajo hogan, healing ceremony, Kee Zonnie, Danny Jim Hatahlie, Buddy Redmustache
      - HDCAM Tape 63, 2002-08-29, AFC 2019/001: MV063; afc2019001_0063; 51 min.; Navajo hogan, healing ceremony, drum-making, Danny Jim Hatahlie
      - HDCAM Tape 64, 2002-08-29, AFC 2019/001: MV064; afc2019001_0064; 48 min.; Navajo hogan, healing ceremony, drum-making, Danny Jim Hatahlie
      - HDCAM Tape 65, 2002-08-30, AFC 2019/001: MV065; afc2019001_0065; 49 min.; Healing ceremony, Monument Valley, petroglyphs
      - HDCAM Tape 66, 2002-08-30, AFC 2019/001: MV066; afc2019001_0066; 50 min.; Navajo sweatbath, basketry, weaving, jewelry, ceremonial dress
      - HDCAM Tape 67, 2002-08-30 to 2002-08-31, AFC 2019/001: MV067; This item is also listed in Series 6, Four Corners Region.; afc2019001_0067; 49 min.; Navajo families, Four Corners Monument
      - HDCAM Tape 71, 2002-09-01, AFC 2019/001: MV071; This item is also listed in Series 6, Four Corners Region.; afc2019001_0071; 39 min.; Four Corners Monument, Monument Valley
    - Sound Recordings
      - DAT Tape 50, 2002-08-28, AFC 2019/001: SR050; afc2019001_DAT0050; 1 hr. 10 min.; Navajo hogan, Kee Zonnie, Buddy Redmustache
      - DAT Tape 51, 2002-08-28, AFC 2019/001: SR051; afc2019001_DAT0051; 1 hr. 7 min.; Navajo hogan, healing ceremony, Kee Zonnie, Buddy Redmustache
      - DAT Tape 52, 2002-08-29, AFC 2019/001: SR052; afc2019001_DAT0052; 1 hr. 17 min.; Danny Jim Hatahlie
      - DAT Tape 53, 2002-08-29, AFC 2019/001: SR053; afc2019001_DAT0053; 1 hr. 13 min.; Songs and prayers, Danny Jim Hatahlie
      - DAT Tape 54, 2002-08-30, AFC 2019/001: SR054; afc2019001_DAT0054; 1 hr. 18 min.; Navajo sweatbath, Danny Jim Hatahlie
      - DAT Tape 55, 2002-08-30 to 2002-08-31, AFC 2019/001: SR055; This item is also listed in Series 6, Four Corners Region.; afc2019001_DAT0055; 1 hr. 19 min.; Danny Jim Hatahlie, Four Corners Monument
      - DAT Tape 57, 2002-08-31 to 2002-09-01, AFC 2019/001: SR057; This item is also listed in Series 6, Four Corners Region.; afc2019001_DAT0057; 1 hr. 13 min.; Four Corners Monument, Monument Valley
  - Four Corners Region, August 30-September 1, 2002
    - Manuscripts
      - Post-production documentation, 2003-10-14, 3 pages; "4 Corners" (Box-folder 2/11)
    - Moving Images
      - HDCAM Tape 67, 2002-08-30 to 2002-08-31, AFC 2019/001: MV067; This item is also listed in Series 6, Navajo Nation.; afc2019001_0067; 49 min.; Navajo families, Four Corners Monument
      - HDCAM Tape 68, 2002-08-30, AFC 2019/001: MV068; afc2019001_0068; 44 min.; Four Corners Monument
      - HDCAM Tape 69, 2002-08-31, AFC 2019/001: MV069; afc2019001_0069; 49 min.; Four Corners Monument
      - HDCAM Tape 70, 2002-08-31, AFC 2019/001: MV070; afc2019001_0070; 49 min.; Four Corners Monument
      - HDCAM Tape 71, 2002-09-01, AFC 2019/001: MV071; This item is also listed in Series 6, Navajo Nation.; afc2019001_0071; 39 min.; Four Corners Monument, Monument Valley
    - Sound Recordings
      - DAT Tape 55, 2002-08-30 to 2002-08-31, AFC 2019/001: SR055; This item is also listed in Series 6, Navajo Nation.; afc2019001_DAT0055; 1 hr. 19 min.; Danny Jim Hatahlie, Four Corners Monument
      - DAT Tape 56, 2002-08-31, AFC 2019/001: SR056; afc2019001_DAT0056; 1 hr. 40 min.; Four Corners Monument
      - DAT Tape 57, 2002-08-31 to 2002-09-01, AFC 2019/001: SR057; This item is also listed in Series 6, Navajo Nation.; afc2019001_DAT0057; 1 hr. 13 min.; Four Corners Monument, Monument Valley
  - Washington (D.C.), September 4-6, 2002
    - Manuscripts
      - Recording logs, 2002-09-04 to 2002-09-05, 4 pages (Box-folder 2/12)
      - Transcriptions, circa 2003-04, 9 pages; English (Box-folder 2/13)
      - Transcription, 2003-02-26, 06_USA_DC_Transcription; 1 file (.jpg); English (Digital-content afc2019001_dc002)
      - Post-production documentation, 2003-10-14, 5 pages; "Ambiances son," "Capitole," "Drapeaux," "ITV Congressman" (Box-folder 2/14)
    - Moving Images
      - HDCAM Tape 72, 2002-09-04, AFC 2019/001: MV072; afc2019001_0072; 49 min.; United States Capitol, The National Mall
      - HDCAM Tape 73, 2002-09-04, AFC 2019/001: MV073; afc2019001_0073; 50 min.; The National Mall, Vietnam Veterans Memorial
      - HDCAM Tape 74, 2002-09-04 to 2002-09-05, AFC 2019/001: MV074; afc2019001_0074; 50 min.; Vietnam Veterans Memorial, Howard Coble
      - HDCAM Tape 75, 2002-09-05 to 2002-09-06, AFC 2019/001: MV075; afc2019001_0075; 55 min.; Howard Coble, Vietnam Veterans Memorial, United States Capitol, National Park Service Survey Lodge
      - HDCAM Tape 76, 2002-09-06, AFC 2019/001: MV076; afc2019001_0076; 48 min.; United States Capitol, Vietnam Veterans Memorial
      - HDCAM Tape 77, 2002-09-06, AFC 2019/001: MV077; afc2019001_0077; 30 min.; Vietnam Veterans Memorial
    - Sound Recordings
      - DAT Tape 58, 2002-09-04, AFC 2019/001: SR058; afc2019001_DAT0058; 1 hr. 35 min.; United States Capitol, Vietnam Veterans Memorial, Washington Monument
      - DAT Tape 59, 2002-09-04 to 2002-09-05, AFC 2019/001: SR059; afc2019001_DAT0059; 1 hr. 28 min.; Vietnam Veterans Memorial, Howard Coble
      - DAT Tape 60, 2002-09-06, AFC 2019/001: SR060; afc2019001_DAT0060; 1 hr. 36 min.; United States Capitol, Vietnam Veterans Memorial
  - Baltimore (Md.), September 7-10, 2002
    - Manuscripts
      - Recording logs, circa 2002-09-07, 2 pages (Box-folder 2/15)
      - Transcription, circa 2003-04, 17 pages; English (Box-folder 2/16)
      - Post-production documentation, 2003-10-14, 2 pages; "Bone dealer" (Box-folder 2/17)
    - Moving Images
      - HDCAM Tape 78, 2002-09-07 to 2002-09-08, AFC 2019/001: MV078; afc2019001_0078; 49 min.; American Dime Museum
      - HDCAM Tape 79, 2002-09-08 to 2002-09-10, AFC 2019/001: MV079; This item is also listed in Series 6, New York (N.Y.).; afc2019001_0079; 49 min.; American Dime Museum, St. Paul's Chapel
    - Sound Recordings
      - DAT Tape 61, 2002-09-08, AFC 2019/001: SR061; afc2019001_DAT0061; 40 min.; American Dime Museum
  - New York (N.Y.), September 8-12, 2002
    - Manuscripts
      - Transcription, circa 2003-04, 9 pages; English (Box-folder 2/18)
      - Post-production documentation, 2003-10-14, 14 pages; "Ground Zero avant cérémonie," "Ground Zero Cérémonie," "Musée NY," "New-York," "ext Mémorial," "int Memorial objets conservés" (Box-folder 2/19)
    - Moving Images
      - HDCAM Tape 79, 2002-09-08 to 2002-09-10, AFC 2019/001: MV079; This item is also listed in Series 6, Baltimore (Md.).; afc2019001_0079; 49 min.; American Dime Museum, St. Paul's Chapel
      - HDCAM Tape 80, 2002-09-10, AFC 2019/001: MV080; afc2019001_0080; 49 min.; St. Paul's Chapel, World Trade Center Site
      - HDCAM Tape 81, 2002-09-10 to 2002-09-11, AFC 2019/001: MV081; afc2019001_0081; 46 min.; World Trade Center Site, first anniversary of 9/11
      - HDCAM Tape 82, 2002-09-11, AFC 2019/001: MV082; afc2019001_0082; 47 min.; World Trade Center Site, first anniversary of 9/11
      - HDCAM Tape 83, 2002-09-11, AFC 2019/001: MV083; afc2019001_0083; 49 min.; World Trade Center Site, first anniversary of 9/11
      - HDCAM Tape 84, 2002-09-11 to 2002-09-12, AFC 2019/001: MV084; afc2019001_0084; 50 min.; World Trade Center Site, first anniversary of 9/11, 9/11 Museum
      - HDCAM Tape 85, 2002-09-12, AFC 2019/001: MV085; afc2019001_0085; 50 min.; 9/11 Museum, Manhattan skyline
      - HDCAM Tape 86, 2002-09-12, AFC 2019/001: MV086; afc2019001_0086; 27 min.; Manhattan skyline
    - Sound Recordings
      - DAT Tape 62, 2002-09-10, AFC 2019/001: SR062; afc2019001_DAT0062; 1 hr. 37 min.; World Trade Center Site
      - DAT Tape 63, 2002-09-10 to 2002-09-11, AFC 2019/001: SR063; afc2019001_DAT0063; 1 hr. 28 min.; St. Paul's Chapel, World Trade Center Site
      - DAT Tape 64, 2002-09-11, AFC 2019/001: SR064; afc2019001_DAT0064; 1 hr. 9 min.; World Trade Center Site
      - DAT Tape 65, 2002-09-12, AFC 2019/001: SR065; afc2019001_DAT0065; 1 hr. 9 min.; 9/11 Museum, Brooklyn Heights, East River
- Series 7: Malaysia
  - George Town (Pulau Pinang), November 7-14, 2002
    - Manuscripts
      - Recording log, 2003-04-17, 07_Malaysia_Georgetown_Recording log; 1 file (.doc) (Digital-content afc2019001_dc002)
      - Translations and transcriptions, 2003-04-16 to 2003-04-18, 71 pages; Hokkien, English, French (Box-folder 2/20)
      - Post-production documentation, 2003-10-14, 20 pages; "Hindu Temple tape 97," "Hindu Temple tape 98," "Hindu Temple," "tape 99," "Oracle," "Funérailles," "Workshop," "Paper maker," "Burmese Temple (+DAT)," "Penang ext shots," "Chinese Temple," "Mosquée," "Thaï Buddhist temple" (Box-folder 2/21)
    - Moving Images
      - HDCAM Tape 87, 2002-11-07, AFC 2019/001: MV087; afc2019001_0087; 49 min.; Goddess of Mercy Temple (Chinese Taoist temple)
      - HDCAM Tape 88, 2002-11-07 to 2002-11-08, AFC 2019/001: MV088; afc2019001_0088; 48 min.; Goddess of Mercy Temple (Chinese Taoist temple), Kapitan Keling Mosque
      - HDCAM Tape 89, 2002-11-08, AFC 2019/001: MV089; afc2019001_0089; 50 min.; Kapitan Keling Mosque, zhizha (paper effigy) workshop
      - HDCAM Tape 90, 2002-11-08 to 2002-11-09, AFC 2019/001: MV090; afc2019001_0090; 49 min.; Zhizha (paper effigy) workshop, fortune teller
      - HDCAM Tape 91, 2002-11-09, AFC 2019/001: MV091; afc2019001_0091; 47 min.; Zhizha (paper effigy) workshop
      - HDCAM Tape 92, 2002-11-09, AFC 2019/001: MV092; afc2019001_0092; 49 min.; Zhizha (paper effigy) workshop, funeral
      - HDCAM Tape 93, 2002-11-09, AFC 2019/001: MV093; afc2019001_0093; 39 min.; Zhizha (paper effigy) workshop, funeral
      - HDCAM Tape 94, 2002-11-09 to 2002-11-10, AFC 2019/001: MV094; afc2019001_0094; 49 min.; Funeral, Goddess of Mercy Temple (Chinese Taoist temple)
      - HDCAM Tape 95, 2002-11-09, AFC 2019/001: MV095; afc2019001_0095; 31 min.; Funeral
      - HDCAM Tape 96, 2002-11-10, AFC 2019/001: MV096; afc2019001_0096; 49 min.; Goddess of Mercy Temple (Chinese Taoist temple), river and skyline views
      - HDCAM Tape 97, 2002-11-10 to 2002-11-12, AFC 2019/001: MV097; afc2019001_0097; 48 min.; River and skyline views, Sri Mahamariamman Temple (Hindu temple)
      - HDCAM Tape 98, 2002-11-12, AFC 2019/001: MV098; afc2019001_0098; 46 min.; Sri Mahamariamman Temple (Hindu temple)
      - HDCAM Tape 99, 2002-11-12 to 2002-11-13, AFC 2019/001: MV099; afc2019001_0099; 49 min.; Sri Mahamariamman Temple (Hindu temple)
      - HDCAM Tape 100, 2002-11-13, AFC 2019/001: MV100; afc2019001_0100; 50 min.; Wat Chayamangkalaram (Thai Buddhist temple), Dhammikarama Burmese Temple (Burmese Buddhist temple)
      - HDCAM Tape 101, 2002-11-13, AFC 2019/001: MV101; afc2019001_0101; 15 min.; Chinese cemetary
    - Sound Recordings
      - DAT Tape 87, 2002-11-07, AFC 2019/001: SR087; afc2019001_DAT0087; 1 hr. 15 min.; Goddess of Mercy Temple (Chinese Taoist temple)
      - DAT Tape 88, 2002-11-08, AFC 2019/001: SR088; afc2019001_DAT0088; 1 hr. 6 min.; Kapitan Keling Mosque
      - DAT Tape 89, 2002-11-08, AFC 2019/001: SR089; afc2019001_DAT0089; 59 min.; Zhizha (paper effigy) workshop, fortune teller
      - DAT Tape 90, 2002-11-09, AFC 2019/001: SR090; afc2019001_DAT0090; 1 hr. 0 min.; Zhizha (paper effigy) workshop
      - DAT Tape 91, 2002-11-09, AFC 2019/001: SR091; afc2019001_DAT0091; 1 hr. 2 min.; Zhizha (paper effigy) workshop
      - DAT Tape 92, 2002-11-09, AFC 2019/001: SR092; afc2019001_DAT0092; 1 hr. 7 min.; Zhizha (paper effigy) workshop, funeral
      - DAT Tape 93, 2002-11-09 to 2002-11-10, AFC 2019/001: SR093; afc2019001_DAT0093; 1 hr. 2 min.; Funeral, Goddess of Mercy Temple (Chinese Taoist temple)
      - DAT Tape 94, 2002-11-10, AFC 2019/001: SR094; afc2019001_DAT0094; 58 min.; Goddess of Mercy Temple (Chinese Taoist temple)
      - DAT Tape 95, 2002-11-12, AFC 2019/001: SR095; afc2019001_DAT0095; 1 hr. 2 min.; Sri Mahamariamman Temple (Hindu temple)
      - DAT Tape 96, 2002-11-12 to 2002-11-13, AFC 2019/001: SR096; afc2019001_DAT0096; 1 hr. 3 min.; Sri Mahamariamman Temple (Hindu temple), Wat Chayamangkalaram (Thai Buddhist temple), Dhammikarama Burmese Temple (Burmese Buddhist temple)
      - DAT Tape 97, 2002-11-13 to 2002-11-14, AFC 2019/001: SR097; afc2019001_DAT0097; 25 min.; Dhammikarama Burmese Temple (Burmese Buddhist temple), Chinese cemetary
- Series 8: Burma
  - Rangoon, November 16-24, 2002
    - Manuscripts
      - Translations and transcriptions, circa 2003-04, This item is also listed in Series 8, Kyaikto.; 36 pages; Burmese, Pali, [Malay?], English (Box-folder 2/22)
      - Post-production documentation, 2003-10-14, 11 pages; "Car shrine," "Shwedagon Paya," "son seuls Shwedagon" (Box-folder 2/23)
    - Moving Images
      - HDCAM Tape 102, 2002-11-16, AFC 2019/001: MV102; afc2019001_0102; 51 min.; Shwedagon Pagoda
      - HDCAM Tape 103, 2002-11-16, AFC 2019/001: MV103; afc2019001_0103; 49 min.; Shwedagon Pagoda
      - HDCAM Tape 104, 2002-11-17, AFC 2019/001: MV104; afc2019001_0104; 48 min.; Shwedagon Pagoda
      - HDCAM Tape 105, 2002-11-17, AFC 2019/001: MV105; afc2019001_0105; 49 min.; Shwedagon Pagoda
      - HDCAM Tape 106, 2002-11-17, AFC 2019/001: MV106; afc2019001_0106; 49 min.; Shwedagon Pagoda
      - HDCAM Tape 107, 2002-11-17, AFC 2019/001: MV107; afc2019001_0107; 36 min.; Shwedagon Pagoda
      - HDCAM Tape 116, 2002-11-23 to 2002-11-24, AFC 2019/001: MV116; This item is also listed in Series 8, Prome.; afc2019001_0116; 49 min.; Shwesandaw Pagoda, Sehtatgyi Paya (giant Buddha statue), Irrawaddy River, Hlawga National Park, Shwenyaungbin Bo Bo Gyi shrine ("car shrine")
      - HDCAM Tape 117, 2002-11-24, AFC 2019/001: MV117; afc2019001_0117; 50 min.; Hlawga National Park, Shwenyaungbin Bo Bo Gyi shrine ("car shrine"), Shwedagon Pagoda
    - Sound Recordings
      - DAT Tape 98, 2002-11-16, AFC 2019/001: SR098; afc2019001_DAT0098; 1 hr. 34 min.; Shwedagon Pagoda
      - DAT Tape 99, 2002-11-16 to 2002-11-17, AFC 2019/001: SR099; afc2019001_DAT0099; 1 hr. 36 min.; Shwedagon Pagoda
      - DAT Tape 100, 2002-11-17, AFC 2019/001: SR100; afc2019001_DAT0100; 1 hr. 39 min.; Shwedagon Pagoda
      - DAT Tape 101, 2002-11-17 to 2002-11-18, AFC 2019/001: SR101; This item is also listed in Series 8, Kyaikto.; afc2019001_DAT0101; 1 hr. 15 min.; Shwedagon Pagoda, Kyaiktiyo Pagoda ("Balancing Boulder")
      - DAT Tape 107, 2002-11-24, AFC 2019/001: SR107; afc2019001_DAT0107; 59 min.; Hlawga National Park, Shwenyaungbin Bo Bo Gyi shrine ("car shrine"), city sounds
  - Kyaikto, November 17-22, 2002
    - Manuscripts
      - Translations and transcriptions, circa 2003-04, This item is also listed in Series 8, Rangoon.; 36 pages; Burmese, Pali, [Malay?], English (Box-folder 2/22)
      - Post-production documentation, 2003-10-14, 8 pages; "Ascension montée et arrivée," "Balancing Boulder," "Collent feuilles d'or" (Box-folder 2/24)
    - Moving Images
      - HDCAM Tape 108, 2002-11-18, AFC 2019/001: MV108; afc2019001_0108; 49 min.; Kyaiktiyo Pagoda ("Balancing Boulder")
      - HDCAM Tape 109, 2002-11-18, AFC 2019/001: MV109; afc2019001_0109; 49 min.; Kyaiktiyo Pagoda ("Balancing Boulder")
      - HDCAM Tape 110, 2002-11-19, AFC 2019/001: MV110; afc2019001_0110; 49 min.; Kyaiktiyo Pagoda ("Balancing Boulder")
      - HDCAM Tape 111, 2002-11-19, AFC 2019/001: MV111; afc2019001_0111; 46 min.; Kyaiktiyo Pagoda ("Balancing Boulder")
      - HDCAM Tape 112, 2002-11-19, AFC 2019/001: MV112; afc2019001_0112; 44 min.; Kyaiktiyo Pagoda ("Balancing Boulder")
      - HDCAM Tape 113, 2002-11-19 to 2002-11-22, AFC 2019/001: MV113; This item is also listed in Series 8, Prome.; afc2019001_0113; 51 min.; Kyaiktiyo Pagoda ("Balancing Boulder"), Shwesandaw Pagoda
    - Sound Recordings
      - DAT Tape 101, 2002-11-17 to 2002-11-18, AFC 2019/001: SR101; This item is also listed in Series 8, Rangoon.; afc2019001_DAT0101; 1 hr. 15 min.; Shwedagon Pagoda, Kyaiktiyo Pagoda ("Balancing Boulder")
      - DAT Tape 102, 2002-11-18 to 2002-11-19, AFC 2019/001: SR102; afc2019001_DAT0102; 1 hr. 35 min.; Kyaiktiyo Pagoda ("Balancing Boulder")
      - DAT Tape 103, 2002-11-19, AFC 2019/001: SR103; afc2019001_DAT0103; 1 hr. 31 min.; Kyaiktiyo Pagoda ("Balancing Boulder")
      - DAT Tape 104, 2002-11-19 to 2002-11-20, AFC 2019/001: SR104; afc2019001_DAT0104; 57 min.; Kyaiktiyo Pagoda ("Balancing Boulder")
  - Prome, November 19-24, 2002
    - Manuscripts
      - Translations and transcriptions, circa 2003-04, 31 pages; [Burmese?], English (Box-folder 2/25)